dealwifi.com 2015-05-16

# Privacy Policy

THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT EXPLAINS THE INFORMATION, COLLECTION AND USE POLICIES OF RAFO TECHNOLOGY INC. AND ANY OF ITS AFFILIATED COMPANIES ("RAFO TECHNOLOGY", “WE” or “US”) WITH RESPECT TO THE WEBSITES, SERVICES, PRODUCTS, TECHNOLOGY, SOFTWARE AND/OR SOFTWARE COMPONENTS (COLLECTIVELY, THE "SOFTWARE & SERVICES") OF RAFO TECHNOLOGY THAT YOU INSTALL, USE, ACCESS OR INTERACT WITH ("USE"), BUT EXCLUDES SOFTWARE AND/OR SERVICES THAT HAVE SEPARATE PRIVACY POLICIES THAT DO NOT INCORPORATE THIS PRIVACY POLICY. BY INSTALLING, USING, ACCESSING AND INTERACTING WITH THE SOFTWARE & SERVICES, YOU CONSENT TO THE DATA PRACTICES AND INFORMATION COLLECTION AS DESCRIBED IN THIS STATEMENT. RAFO TECHNOLOGY IS COMMITTED TO PRESERVING THE PRIVACY OF ITS USERS. THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT EXPLAINS WHAT INFORMATION WE MAY COLLECT AND HOW WE MAY USE IT.  
IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS SET FORTH HEREIN, DO NOT USE THE SOFTWARE & SERVICES. 

By selecting "Set Deal WiFI as your homepage" checkbox on Deal WiFI installer primary notice, "Search App by Deal WiFI” extension will be installed to your Chrome.

### Information Collection and Use

Our primary goals in collecting information are to provide and improve our service, the Application and features and content relating thereto (together, the Service) and to enable users to enjoy the Service. Information we collect may include:

Device-specific information – including hard drive serial number and machine name, hardware, hardware model, operating system version, unique device identifiers. With these information, we’ll be able to make sure the software can be run smoothly on your device, as when our service is being visited, we may automatically collect and store certain information in server logs locally.

When you Use the Software & Services, we automatically generate an anonymous internal user ID (which does not personally identify you), which is assigned to your use of the Software & Services (the "User ID") and may be combined with any of the above information.

While it is not our intention to collect any personally identifiable information (“PII”) (except for registration and user support purposes as set forth in this Privacy Policy), the data collected may include PII. As part of our privacy measures, we implement certain rules designed to avoid the unintentional collection of PII such as email addresses, social security numbers, credit card numbers, login information etc. Such rules are based on known field types, parameters, values and algorithms but they are not foolproof and hence the Software & Services may sometimes, unintentionally, collect unwanted information. We regularly examine and update these rules.

Search information – if you consent to homepage setting, we may collect your search terms and share with our partners. The search feature, in the course of processing a given search query, will send a request to our servers. This request includes the keyword query, time of day, browser type, default language setting, and IP address, an anonymous unique ID. We use this information to properly process your search request. For example, this data provides us with information on which language you prefer to use and your geographical location. Such information is recorded on a non-personally identifiable basis, is kept strictly anonymous and is Non-Identifying Information. In addition, all information about search activity is evaluated only on an aggregated basis (except in response to a customer service inquiry or legal process).

### Information Sharing and Disclosure

Aggregate Information and Non-Identifying Information. We may share aggregated information that does not include Personal Information and we may otherwise disclose Non-Identifying Information with third parties for industry analysis, demographic profiling and other purposes. Any aggregated information shared in these contexts will not contain your Personal Information.

Service Providers. We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service, to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related actions (e.g., without limitation, maintenance services, database management, web analytics and improvement of the Site or Application's features) or to assist us in analyzing how our application are used. These third parties have access to your Information only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.

Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement. RAFO TECHNOLOGY cooperates with government and law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We will disclose any information we have to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal process (including but not limited to subpoenas), to protect the property and rights of RAFO TECHNOLOGY or a third party, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop activity we may consider to be, or to pose a risk of being, any illegal, unethical or legally actionable activity.

We may, from time to time, change this Privacy Policy. We encourage you to visit and review this Policy frequently to stay informed. Prior to any material change to this Privacy Policy, RAFO TECHNOLOGY will present you with a detailed notification (e.g. a pop-up notification or other reasonable means) of such change including information on how you may uninstall the Software & Services. Other changes, including amendments made to the Policy to comply with legal requirements, will become effective immediately upon their initial posting. RAFO TECHNOLOGY will also update the "Last updated” date at the end of this Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the Software & Services after any change takes effect will indicate your acceptance of the amended Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with any of the amended terms, you must avoid any further use of the Software & Services.

### Security

We implement measures to secure your PII that we collect in order to minimize the risks of damage, loss of information, and unauthorized access or use of information. However, these measures are unable to provide absolute information security. Therefore, although we make efforts to secure your PII, we cannot guarantee and you cannot reasonably expect that the Software & Services and its databases are immune from any wrongdoings, malfunctions, unauthorized interceptions, access or other kinds of abuse and misuse.

### Contacting Us

If you have any concerns or questions with respect to any matter covered by this Privacy Policy, you may contact us by email at:  
Company Name: RAFO TECHNOLOGY INC.  
Address: 245 EAST MAIN STREET, SUITE 115 ENTITY CITY, United STATE, ZIP:ALHAMBRA CA91801  
Email:[dealwifi@rafotech.com](mailto:dealwifi@rafotech.com)
